Maedeh Mosayebi

Product Designer

+98-913-646-5849 | maedehmosayebi@gmail.com | maedehmosayebi.github.io/me | dribbble.com/maedeMSBI

ABOUT ME

A creative Product Designer with over 6 years of experience in UI and UX design and problem-solving, including designing solutions for C2C, B2C, and B2Bs. Made complex tasks simple, accessible, and beautiful for millions of users through human-centered design.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Product designer

Taaghche: A bookshop and book reader

06 / 2020 - PRESENT

- Working with cross-functional teams in a Scrum structure with product managers, researchers,
 UX writers, and engineers, to execute impactful product experience in each KPIs and OKRs.
- Lead multiple projects for design from strategy to lunch and devised new operational processes that increased productivity.
- Conducted more than 30 **surveys**, 40 **usability tests**, heuristic evaluations, and benchmarking analyses and presented findings and design recommendations.
- Designed desktop and mobile websites, iOS, Android, and windows applications.
- Designed a new business line that increase the financial bottom line to 120%.

Product designer

03 / 2018 - 06 / 2020

Shetab: Pre-employment tests platform

- Lead the design for wholly new experiences and improvements existing and making new experiences while planning and defining strategies and solutions for +1M users.
- Quickly iterate on multiple interactive design solutions and work through details and engage directly with users to test design solutions.
- Analyzing 20,000 data points and 54 survey responses to design pre-employment tests.
- Taking more than 50 usability tests, 8 **cart-sorting**, 12 **A/B testing**, and leveraging the results and analysis to make better design decisions.
- Actively participate in product planning with the product leads.
- Create a standard Design System with rules and principles, color palette, **typography**, and **icons**.

Product designer 05 / 2016 - 01 / 2018

Dehkadeh NoAvari: CPE Manufacturer

- Designing a user-friendly dashboard led to a 35% increase in revenue.
- Laying out a vision around how the consumer product scales to a future with multiple lines of business and fulfillment types.
- Designed the box of the NJM modem/router, brochures, and posters.
- Working on SaaS Product and Android and iOS, desktop, and web dashboards for managing the Modem/Router.

BackEnd Developer

02/2016 - 05/2016

Kasra: Online attendance system for companies

• Utilizing Node.js, Socket.io, and Angular for website architecture and real-time update technology.

FrontEnd Developer

02 / 2015 - 11 / 2015

CPOL: Ordering/Logistics platform

• Designed dynamic and multi-browser pages using HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JQuery, Angular JS.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Design:
 - Illustration
 - UI graphics
 - Strategy & Vision presentations
 - User flows
 - Concept sketches
 - Wireframes and Mockups
 - Motion design (SVG & AfterEffects)
 - Style guides and pattern library
 - Prototyping
- Tools:
 - Adobe XD
 - Adobe Illustrator
 - Adobe After Effect
 - Figma
 - Sketch
 - Zeplin
 - HTML / CSS / JS

Research:

- Data analysis
- Persona hypothesis
- Task analysis
- Usability testing
- A/B Testing
- Contextual inquiry
- Information-architecture
- Comparative analysis

Soft:

- Self Starter
- Detail-oriented
- Flexible
- Communicative
- Independence
- Teamwork
- Organized

EDUCATION

University of Isfahan

2017

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

Iran, Isfahan

LANGUAGES Persian: Fluent | English: B2

2